<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Confirm4Crit</title>
    <link>http://Confirm4Crit.com/tags/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Confirm4Crit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 12:29:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://Confirm4Crit.com/tags/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals of 2017</title>
      <link>http://confirm4crit.com/post/2017-Goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 12:29:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://confirm4crit.com/post/2017-Goals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just wanted to write down a few things I intend to do in the new year. Only really writing it down to make myself obligated to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete some web stack development courses on PluralSight. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I touched Angular,Django, and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind getting something done from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get a basic app up and running on iOS from scratch. I&amp;rsquo;ve ported Unity stuff to iOS, but nothing much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participate in more game jams. I think I did .5 game jams last year, let&amp;rsquo;s see if I can bump that up a little. It certainly helped me explore stuff and fail faster, especially in VR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sub goal: Hopefully one of the above spins to a pet project that I grind out more on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start streaming more. Don&amp;rsquo;t really know what game, or when, but I enjoyed what little I did in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe do a speed run of something? Not expecting anything close, just wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind chasing at a record of something for a bit, even if I have no chance to get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cut soda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Impressions</title>
      <link>http://confirm4crit.com/post/Hugo-Impressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 12:29:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://confirm4crit.com/post/Hugo-Impressions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Been fiddling with Hugo the past week, tweaking the site here and there to fit what I need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been exciting hosting my own little site to hold all of &lt;strong&gt;me&lt;/strong&gt;. Resume, portfolio, personal thoughts, etc. I had too much moving around, Tumblr, Twitter, all my AscendedAlpaca blogs, etc. Nice just to have it all &lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also got my first pull request excepted. It&amp;rsquo;s insignificant, but it was need feeling contributing to a project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/yoshiharuyamashita/blackburn/pull/31&#34;&gt;Here it is&lt;/a&gt;, if anyone cares. I added a Tumblr social link on my own to the side bar, so I figured to slap in on the main theme, and it got accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feels neat.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://confirm4crit.com/post/My-First-Post-with-Hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 18:55:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://confirm4crit.com/post/My-First-Post-with-Hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post fiddling with Hugo. Seems like a great tool for this blog. &lt;strong&gt;Yay!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>